ظآزThe whole world is lit upظآز
ظآزBecause you existظآز
ظآزYou're alwaysظآز
ظآزSomewhere close, flying with meظآز
ظآزGo to where the wind blowsظآز
ظآزHold tightظآز
ظآزTo the ray of light that belongs to usظآز
=Wild & Fiery=
=Episode 13=
Ms. Mu,
Mr. Mu specifically instructed
that you must fulfill his last wish.
Only then
will you be able to inherit the estate.
(Last Will)
(Marry and have a child
whose surname follows the mother's.)
(Only after fulfilling this condition will
the other inheritance terms take effect.)
(Marriage?)
(Have a child
whose surname follows the mother's?)
Zhiyu,
what did your dad write in the will?
That's none of your business.
You don't need to know.
My heart breaks
seeing Zhiyu like this.
She probably still can't accept
her dad's death.
Since Zhiyu isn't in the right mood
to tell me.
How about
you tell me instead, Mr. Wang?
This might
involve Ms. Mu's privacy.
If it's to be made public,
we should first get her permission.
As his wife,
am I not qualified
to know my husband's will?
Uh...
Mr. Wang,
although Chenzhou has passed away,
you can still
continue working with the Mu Group.
In the will, Mr. Mu required
that Ms. Mu must get married
and promised that the child
she gives birth to will take her surname.
Only then will she qualify
to inherit the estate.
(So Yu has to get married?)
(This old geezer really
went to great lengths)
(to stop me from seizing
the family fortune.)
(But as for Mu Zhiyu's future husband,)
(I've already arranged that for her.)
What did the will say
to make you this uneasy?
If I want to inherit the estate,
I have to get married first.
And if I have a child,
the child must take my mother's surname.
(Marriage.)
(Child takes the mother's surname.)
(Chairman Mu was extremely meticulous.)
(He set up protection against Xu Mingzhu
with this one will,)
(prevented her from taking power directly,
protected his daughter,)
(and ensured the family lineage
would continue.)
(Impressive.)
What I don't understand is
that I'm his only daughter.
Why do I have to get married first
before inheriting the estate?
Maybe he hoped this would
bring you back to him.
Or maybe
it was meant to guard against
Xu Mingzhu,
so you wouldn't be left alone
and helpless.
Do you understand?
Thank you, Shen Jibai.
Thank you for being there for me.
Shen Jibai!
Don't touch Yu!
Mr. He,
you're overstepping.
This is a private area.
You're just a bodyguard.
How dare you lay your hands
on your employee? You...
Enough.
All of you, leave.
I want to be alone for a while.
Yu.
ظآزListen, the wind chime is ringingظآز
ظآزI wish to forget youظآز
ظآزBut I'm powerless to keep livingظآز
ظآزThe scenery you once said
you wanted to seeظآز
Don't come out alone like this again.
It's dangerous.
ظآزYou asked me to see it for you insteadظآز
No matter where I am,
can you always find me?
Finding you
and protecting you
is my duty.
Will you always protect me?
I will.
ظآزYour freedomظآز
ظآزHas become my prisonظآز
Drink with me.
ظآزMy hand brushed across the smile
on the photoظآز
ظآزA cup of wine full of sorrowظآز
ظآزLooking up,
there's the beautiful starry skyظآز
Are you still upset about the will?
ظآزYou told meظآز
ظآزIt would shine like the starsظآز
ظآزBut you forgot to tell meظآز
I just wanted
to get some fresh air.
And I happened
to feel like drinking.
I want a drink too.
ظآزYour gentle faceظآز
ظآزI'm tiredظآز
ظآزYou are far awayظآز
ظآزGo on. Take your camera
and go travelingظآز
ظآزI want to turn back
and walk with youظآز
You drank all my beer.
ظآزYour freedomظآز
We had the beer
and enjoyed the fresh air.
Let's go back.
ظآزMy hand brushed across the smile
on the photoظآز
ظآزA cup of wine full of sorrowظآز
ظآزLooking up,
there's the beautiful starry skyظآز
ظآزYou told meظآز
ظآزIt would shine like the starsظآز
You're drunk.
Don't move.
I'm not drunk.
ظآزLooking up,
there's the beautiful starry skyظآز
I'll take you back.
Don't leave me.
Don't worry.
I will never leave you.
ظآزLight comes beaming inظآز
ظآزLanding on my skinظآز
ظآزWarms the space you left behindظآز
ظآزShadows move aroundظآز
ظآزAwake, racing thoughtsظآز
ظآزTry to keep the memories safeظآز
ظآزDon't slip awayظآز
ظآزI'm all yours, all yoursظآز